const QuestionList = [
  {
    question:
      "Almatti Dam is on which of the following rivers?   ",
    answers: ["Krishna", "Kaveri", "Tungabhadra", "Malprabha"],
    correct: "Krishna",
    questionId: "1",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following states is India’s largest Bauxite producer"?',
    answers: ["Odisha", "Jharkhand", "Rajasthan", "Karnataka"],
    correct: "Jharkhand",
    questionId: "2",
  },
  {
    question:
      "With which of the following countries, India shares maximum length of border?",
    answers: ["Pakistan", "China", "Bangladesh", "Nepal"],
    correct: "Bangladesh",
    questionId: "3",
  },
  {
    question: "Amaravati, Arkavathy, Bhavani, Chinnar, Hemavati, Honnuhole, Kabini etc. Are tributaries of which among the following rivers?",
    answers: [
      "Kaveri",
      "Krishna",
      "Godavri",
      "Narmada",
    ],
    correct: "Kaveri",
    questionId: "4",
  },
  {
    question: "Amaravati, Arkavathy, Bhavani, Chinnar, Hemavati, Honnuhole, Kabini etc. Are tributaries of which among the following rivers?",
    answers: ["Sikkim", "Meghalaya", "Arunachal pradesh", "Manipur"],
    correct: "Arunachal pradesh",
    questionId: "5",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Indravati Hydro Electric Project belongs to which state?",
    answers: [
      "Tamil nadu",
      "Orissa",
      "Karnataka",
      "Andhra pradesh",
    ],
    correct: "Orrisa",
    questionId: "6",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which among the following is the origin of Damodar river ?',
    answers: ["Greater Himalaya", "MKumaon Himalaya", "Shayadri Hills", "Chota Nagpur"],
    correct: "Chota Nagpur",
    questionId: "7",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The following hills are present where Eastern Ghats and Western Ghats meet ?   ",
    answers: ["Cardamom Hills", "Anamalai Hills", "TNilgiri hills", "Shayadri hills"],
    correct: "Nilgiri Hills",
    questionId: "8",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Bring out the only incorrect statement?",
    answers: [
      "Maximum Jute Mills in India are in West Bengal",
      "Maximum Jute Mills in India are in Cooperative Sector",
      "KMaximum Wool produced in India is of Carpet Grade",
      "Maximum woolen units in decentralized sector in India are in Punjab",
    ],
    correct: "Maximum Jute Mills in India are in Cooperative Sector",
    questionId: "9",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Mullaperiyar Dam” has been a long pending issue between which of the following two states?   ",
    answers: ["Karnataka & Kerala", "KAndhra Pradesh and Tamil Nadu", "Karnataka & Tamil Nadu", "Tamil Nadu and Kerala"],
    correct: "Tamil Nadu and Kerala",
    questionId: "10",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the approximate length of the Brahmaputra Plain?   ",
    answers: ["500 km", "720 km", "T1130 km", "1450 km"],
    correct: "720 km",
    questionId: "11",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is the highest peak of the Himalayan range in India?   ",
    answers: ["K2", "Kanchenjunga", "Nanda Devi", "Mt.Everest"],
    correct: "Kanchenjunga",
    questionId: "12",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Nathu La Pass is situated in which of the following range?   ",
    answers: ["Vindhyas", "Karakoram", "Western Ghat", "Himalayas"],
    correct: "Western Ghat",
    questionId: "13",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Ananthagiri Hills is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
    answers: ["Madhya Pradesh", "Telangana", "Chattisgarh", "West Bengal"],
    correct: "Telangana",
    questionId: "14",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Mount Abu is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
    answers: ["Rajasthan", "Madhya Pradesh", "Uttar Pradesh", "Karnataka"],
    correct: "Rajasthan",
    questionId: "15",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is the new name of the Ross island?   ",
    answers: ["Mahatma Gandhi Island", "Abdul Kalam Island", "Jawaharlal Nehru Island", "Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose Island"],
    correct: "Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose Island",
    questionId: "16",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is the longest Drive-In Beach in Asia?   ",
    answers: ["Muzhappilangad Beach", "Kollam Beach", "Marari beach", "Fort Kochi beach"],
    correct: "Muzhappilangad Beach",
    questionId: "17",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Katchh & Kathiawar Peninsula are separated from each other by which of the following gulfs/ Bays?   ",
    answers: ["Gulf of Katchh", "Gulf of Khambat", "Gulf of Mannar", "Gulf of Aden"],
    correct: "Gulf of Katchh",
    questionId: "18",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Bhander Plateau is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
    answers: ["Madhya Pradesh", "Jharkhand", "Maharashtra", "Karnataka"],
    correct: "Madhya Pradesh",
    questionId: "19",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is the northern most island of Nicobar island?   ",
    answers: ["Little Nicobar", "Car Nicobar", "Great Nicobar", "Teressa island"],
    correct: "Car Nicobar",
    questionId: "20",
  },
  {
    question:
    "Damodar through divided ranchi plateau in the north from which of the following plateau?",
    answers: ["Koderma Plateau", "Hazaribagh Plateau", "Singhbhum Plateau", "None of the above"],
    correct: "Hazaribagh Plateau",
    questionId: "21",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Meghalaya Plateau is detached from the Indian peninsula by which of the following?   ",
    answers: ["Great Boundary Fault", "Himalayan Frontal Fault", "Goranghat gap", "Malda Gap"],
    correct: "Malda Gap",
    questionId: "22",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The southern part of the Karnataka plateau is known as by which of the following name?   ",
    answers: ["Barkhan", "Malnad", "Maidan", " Hamada"],
    correct: "Maidan",
    questionId: "23",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Sigur Plateau is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
    answers: ["Karnataka", "Kerala", "Andhra Pradesh", "Tamil Nadu"],
    correct: "Tamil Nadu",
    questionId: "24",
  },
  {
    question:
    " Zuari river is located in which of the following states of India?   ",
    answers: ["Goa", " Maharashtra", " Kerala", "Arunachal Pradesh"],
    correct: "Goa",
    questionId: "25",
  },






  {
    question:
      "“Shesher Kabita” is the reknowned work of which among the following legends?   ",
    answers: ["Rabindranath Tagore", "Bibhutibhushan Bandopadhyay", "Narendranath Mitra", "Dinabandhu Mitra"],
    correct: "Rabindranath Tagore",
    questionId: "26",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Mattur Village, whose inhabitants are known to speak Sanskrit Language is located in which among the following states of India?   ",
    answers: ["Andhra Pradesh", "Karnataka", "Kerala", "Tamil Nadu"],
    correct: "Karnataka",
    questionId: "27",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Dhundiraj Govind was the first name of which of the following legends of Indian Cinema?   ",
    answers: ["Dada Saheb Phalke", "Dev Anand", "Guru Datt", "Prithviraj Kapoor"],
    correct: "Dada Saheb Phalke",
    questionId: "28",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The following places represent the contemporary 4 Dhamas of Hindu Pilgrimage in India?   ",
      answers: [
        "Badrinath -Kedarnath – Amarnath – Vaishnodevi",
        "Badrinath – Kedarnatrh – Gangotri – Yamunotri",
        "Badrinath – Kedarnath – Rameshwaram – Puri",
        "Badrinath -Rameshwaram -Puri -Dwarka",
      ],
      correct: "Badrinath -Rameshwaram -Puri -Dwarkar",
      questionId: "29",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Vedantham Satyanarayan is known to be a greatest guru of which of the following dance forms?   ",
    answers: ["Odissi", "kathak", "Bharatnatyam", " Kuchipudi"],
    correct: " Kuchipudi",
    questionId: "30",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The best known of the compilations of the compositions of Kabir are known as ?   ",
    answers: ["Shatapadi", " Dohavali", "Bijak", "Kavitavali"],
    correct: "Bijak",
    questionId: "31",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The only Dravidian language that is spoken entirely outside India is ___ ?   ",
    answers: [" Tulu", "Kurukh", "Brahui", "Gondi"],
    correct: "Brahui",
    questionId: "32",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Paika Akhada is also known as sword fighting. This martial art is predominantly practised in which state of India?   ",
    answers: ["Rajasthan", "Maharashtra", "Odisha", "Tamil Nadu"],
    correct: "Odisha",
    questionId: "33",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Kovai Kora cotton saris, which received the GI status in 2014, are manufactured in which state?   ",
    answers: ["Maharashtra", "Karnataka", "Tamil Nadu", "Andhra Pradesh"],
    correct: "Tamil Nadu",
    questionId: "34",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Saga Dawa festival marks the life of Buddha. It is most commonly celebrated in which state?   ",
    answers: ["Jammu & Kashmir", " Sikkim", "Assam", "Maharashtra"],
    correct: " Sikkim",
    questionId: "35",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Rashtriya Sanskriti Mahotsav for the year 2017 will be held at which of the following places?   ",
      answers: [
        "Srinagar, Jammu and Kashmir",
        "Tawang, Arunachal Pradesh",
        "Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh",
        "Amaravati, Andhra Pradesh",
      ],
      correct: "Tawang, Arunachal Pradesh",
      questionId: "36",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Muktesvara temple of  Orissa was built in which of the following centuries?   ",
    answers: ["6th century AD", "8th century AD", "9th century AD", "10th century AD"],
    correct: "10th century AD",
    questionId: "37",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following authors wrote Kadambarikathasara?   ",
    answers: ["Rajanaka Ratnakar", "Jinasena", "Sanmitracharita", " Abhinanda"],
    correct: " Abhinanda",
    questionId: "38",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The writers named Prithusvami, Bhattotpala and Vijavanandi belong to which of the following centuries?   ",
    answers: ["9th", " 10th", "11th", "12th"],
    correct: "10th",
    questionId: "39",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following wrote Yogavarttika and Yogasarasamgraha?   ",
    answers: ["Vijnanabhikshu", "Udayana", "Jayanta", "Nathamuni"],
    correct: "Vijnanabhikshu",
    questionId: "40",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The sufi philosophy is primarily based on the concept of which of the following?   ",
    answers: ["Unity with beloved", "Unity with god", "Unity with universe", "Unity with universe"],
    correct: "Unity with god",
    questionId: "41",
  },
  {
    question:
      "With reference to Sufism, which of the following term refers to divine proximity?   ",
    answers: [" Qurbat", "Ruh", "Hulul", "Fana"],
    correct: " Qurbat",
    questionId: "42",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following was also known as Baba Farid Ganj-i Shakar?   ",
    answers: ["Qutbuddin Bakhtiyar Kaki", "Fariduddin Masud", "Khwaja Muinuddin Chishti", "Nizamuddin Auliya"],
    correct: "Fariduddin Masud",
    questionId: "43",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following saints founded the Sabiri branch of Chisti order?   ",
    answers: ["Makhdurn Alauddin Ali", "Abdul Quddus Gangohi", "Muhibbullah Allahabadi", "Salim Chishti"],
    correct: "Makhdurn Alauddin Ali",
    questionId: "44",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the practice adopted by Hindus of engaging in lifelong monasticism in order to achieve Moksha at the last stage of their lives?   ",
    answers: ["Yoga", "Sanyasa", "Puja", " Sadhna"],
    correct: "Sanyasa",
    questionId: "45",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What are major sub-traditions of Jainism called?   ",
    answers: ["Digambaras", " Svetambaras", "Both of the above", "None of the above"],
    correct: "Both of the above",
    questionId: "46",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In how many forms is Hindu religiosity mentioned?   ",
    answers: ["Four", "Five", " Six", "Three"],
    correct: " Four",
    questionId: "47",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is text on rituals, ceremonies, sacrifices and symbolic-sacrifices?   ",
    answers: ["Aranyakas", "Brahmanas", "Both of the above", "None of the above"],
    correct: "Both of the above",
    questionId: "48",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Suhrawardi order was popularized in Kashmir by which of the following saint?   ",
    answers: ["Makhdum Jahaniyah", "Makhdum Hamzah", "Shihabuddin Suhrawardi", "Bahauddin Zakariya"],
    correct: "Makhdum Hamzah",
    questionId: "49",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which year did Vivekananda participate in the Parliament of the World’s Religions?   ",
    answers: ["1893 AD", "1895 AD", "1897 AD", "1899 AD"],
    correct: "1893 AD",
    questionId: "50",
  },





  
  {
    question:
      "Effective TB treatment is difficult because of the unusual structure and chemical composition of the which among the following parts of the cells of Tuberculosis Bacteria (Mycobacterium tuberculosis)?   ",
    answers: ["Cell membrane", "Cell wall", "Nucleus", "Plasama"],
    correct: "Cell wall",
    questionId: "51",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Lac is the scarlet resinous secretion from ________?   ",
    answers: [" Herbs", "  Trees", "Bark", " insects"],
    correct: " insects",
    questionId: "52",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which among the following is a character of Chloroplast which makes them qualified to self replication?   ",
    answers: ["Presence of DNA", "Presence of RNA", "Presence of Both DNA & RNA", "Absence of Both DNA & RNA"],
    correct: "Presence of Both DNA & RNA",
    questionId: "53",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Plants growing on marshy areas are commonly called as _____??   ",
    answers: ["Oxylophytes", "Lithophytes", "Helophytes", "Psilophytes"],
    correct: "Helophytes",
    questionId: "54",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which organelle is associated with formation of basal granules & flagella?   ",
    answers: [" Centrosome", "Golgi apparatus", "Mitochondria", "Lysosome "],
    correct: " Centrosome",
    questionId: "55",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The recoiling of gun is an example of which of the following?   ",
      answers: [
        "Law of Conservation of Angular Momentum",
        "Law of Conservation of Linear Momentum",
        "Conversion of Kinetic Energy to Potential Energy",
        "Law of Conservation of Energy",
      ],
      correct: "Law of Conservation of Linear Momentum",
      questionId: "56",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following represents the Density of a material?   ",
    answers: ["Mass/weight", "Mass/Length", "Mass/Volume", "Mass/Area"],
    correct: "Mass/Volume",
    questionId: "57",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What are the oscillations of a body whose amplitude goes on decreasing with time called as?   ",
    answers: ["Free oscillation", "Maintained oscillation", "Forced oscillation", "Damped oscillation"],
    correct: "Damped oscillation",
    questionId: "58",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the S.I. unit of absorptive power?   ",
    answers: ["dioptre", "metre", " ampere", "No unit"],
    correct: "No unit",
    questionId: "59",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following part of eyes controls the size of the pupil?   ",
    answers: ["Retina", "iris", "Cornea", "None of the above"],
    correct: "iris",
    questionId: "60",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the property of a conductor to resist the flow of charges known as?   ",
    answers: ["Conductance", "Conductivity", "Resistance", "Electric Potential"],
    correct: "Resistance",
    questionId: "61",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the susceptibility of a diamagnetic material?   ",
    answers: ["positive and small", "positive and large", "negative", "None"],
    correct: "negative",
    questionId: "62",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the source of energy in nuclear reactors which produce electricity?   ",
    answers: ["Nuclear Fission", "Nuclear Fusion", "Gamma decay", "None of the above"],
    correct: "Nuclear Fission",
    questionId: "63",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is a law of reflection?   ",
      question:
      "The recoiling of gun is an example of which of the following?   ",
      answers: [
        "angle of incidence is equal to the angle of reflection",
        "angle of incidence is equal to twice the angle of reflection",
        "angle of incidence is equal to half of the angle of reflectiony",
        "angle of incidence is always complimentary to the angle of reflection",
      ],
      correct: "angle of incidence is equal to the angle of reflection",
      questionId: "64",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the fuel in the Sun?   ",
    answers: ["Helium", "Hydrogen", " Oxygen", "Carbon dioxide"],
    correct: "Hydrogen",
    questionId: "65",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What do we call the reactions in which there is an exchange of ions between the reactants?   ",
    answers: ["Double Displacement reaction", "Decomposition reaction", "Displacement reaction", "Combination reaction"],
    correct: "Double Displacement reactions",
    questionId: "66",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What do we call the molecular orbital obtained by subtraction of atomic orbitals?   ",
    answers: ["Bonding orbital", "Anti-bonding orbital", "Lateral orbital", "Sub-orbital"],
    correct: "Anti-bonding orbital",
    questionId: "67",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a strong electrolyte?   ",
    answers: ["HCl", "KOH", "H2CO3", "NaoH"],
    correct: "H2CO3",
    questionId: "68",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is Hydroponics?   ",
    answers: ["process of growing plants without using soil", "process of growing flowers", "process of growing fruits", "process of cultivating garden"],
    correct: "process of growing plants without using soil",
    questionId: "69",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which among the following metals is the hardest metal?   ",
    answers: ["Platinum", "Gold", "Iron", "Tungsten"],
    correct: "Tungsten",
    questionId: "70",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which element helped James Chadwick to discover Neutron?   ",
    answers: ["Lithium", "Beryllium", "Boron", "Carbon"],
    correct: "Beryllium",
    questionId: "71",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which country hosted the Ministerial Roundtable Dialogue on Biodiversity in September 2020?   ",
    answers: ["India", "China", "United States", "Germany"],
    correct: "China",
    questionId: "72",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following branch of biology deals with the study of Cartilage?   ",
    answers: ["Chondrology", "Chromatology", "Cnidology", "Conchology"],
    correct: "Chondrology",
    questionId: "73",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following biologist is related to Cell Theory?   ",
    answers: ["Carl Linnaeus", "Theophrastus", "Theodor Schwann", "Francis Galton"],
    correct: "Theodor Schwann",
    questionId: "74",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is another name for cyanobacteria?   ",
    answers: ["Blue-green algae", "Protists", "Golden algae", "Slime moulds"],
    correct: "Blue-green algae",
    questionId: "75",
  },





  {
    question:
      "Who is the head of Indian Constitution?   ",
    answers: ["President", "Prime Minister", " Governor", "Home Minister"],
    correct: "President",
    questionId: "76",
  },
  {
    question:
      " Who was the first female governor of India?   ",
    answers: ["Sarojini Devi", "Lata Devi", "Indira Gandhi", "Vijay Laxmi"],
    correct: "Sarojini Devi",
    questionId: "77",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the first Deputy Chairman of Planning Commission?   ",
    answers: ["Vijay Lakshmi Pandit", "Lata Devi", "Gulzari lal Nanda", "Sarojini Devi"],
    correct: "Gulzari lal Nanda",
    questionId: "78",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which is the largest union territory in India?   ",
    answers: ["Lakshadweep", "Andaman", "Nicobar", "Pondicherry"],
    correct: "Pondicherry",
    questionId: "79",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which court is the Oldest High Court in India?   ",
    answers: ["Madras High Court", "Calcutta High Court", "Bombay High Court", "Delhi High Court"],
    correct: "Calcutta High Court",
    questionId: "80",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Right to property was removed from the list of Fundamental Rights during the rule of ……….?   ",
    answers: ["Shastri Government", "Indira Gandhi Government", "Nehru Government", "Morarji Desai Government"],
    correct: "Morarji Desai Government",
    questionId: "81",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the legal advisor to the State Government?   ",
    answers: ["Advocate – General", " Advocate", "General", "Judge"],
    correct: "Advocate – General",
    questionId: "82",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The first state to adopt the panchayat raj in India is ……?   ",
    answers: ["Gujrat", "Assam", "Madhya Pradesh", "Rajasthan"],
    correct: "Rajasthan",
    questionId: "83",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which country is the source for the fundamental Duties?   ",
    answers: ["India", "Japan", " Russia", "America"],
    correct: "Russia",
    questionId: "84",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record of winning Lok Sabha election with the highest margin of votes?   ",
    answers: ["Morarji Desai", "Atal Bihari Bajpayi", " Shastri", "Anil Basu"],
    correct: "Anil Basu",
    questionId: "85",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who appoints the Attorney General of India?   ",
    answers: ["Lok Sabha", "Parliament", "Rajya Sabha", "Supreme court"],
    correct: "Parliament",
    questionId: "86",
  },
  {
    question:
      "To which of the following states, Article 370 if the Indian constitution is related:?   ",
    answers: ["Arunachal Pradesh", "Meghalaya", "Himachal Pradesh", "Jammu & Kashmir"],
    correct: "Jammu & Kashmir",
    questionId: "87",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Indian state has its own constitution?   ",
    answers: ["Sikkim", "Arunachal Pradesh", "Meghalaya", "None of these"],
    correct: "None of these",
    questionId: "88",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Under which ministry, Directorate General of Foreign Trade (DGFT) organisation comes:?   ",
    answers: ["Ministry of Finance", "Ministry of Commerce and Industry", "Ministry of Foreign Trade", "Home Ministry"],
    correct: "Ministry of Commerce and Industry",
    questionId: "89",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Where is the head quarter of the Directorate General of Foreign Trade (DGFT)?   ",
    answers: ["Mumbai", "Bangaluru", "New Delhi", "Kolkata"],
    correct: "New Delhi",
    questionId: "90",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Indian constitution took the concept of single citizenship from?   ",
    answers: ["USA", "UK", " Australia", "Japan"],
    correct: "UK",
    questionId: "91",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which article of the Constitution contains the provisions of citizenship to persons migrated to India from Pakistan?   ",
    answers: ["Article 5", "Article 6", "Article 7", "Article 8"],
    correct: "Article 6",
    questionId: "92",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Indian citizenship can be acquired through which of the following?   ",
    answers: ["By descent", "By naturalization", "By registration   ", "All of above"],
    correct: "All of above",
    questionId: "93",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Union budget of India is referred in which of the following article:?   ",
    answers: ["Article 109", "Article 112", "Article  180", "Article 212"],
    correct: "Article 112",
    questionId: "94",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The first Union budget of independent India was presented by ?   ",
    answers: ["Jawahar Lal Nehru", "Vallabh Bhai Patel", "R. K. Shanmukham Chetty", "Morarji Ranchhodji Desai"],
    correct: "R. K. Shanmukham Chetty",
    questionId: "95",
  },
  {
    question:
      "When was IRDA established?   ",
    answers: ["1965", "1954", "1999", "2001"],
    correct: "1999",
    questionId: "96",
  },
  {
    question:
      "To whom the Speaker of the Lok Sabha gives his resignation?   ",
    answers: ["President", "Chief justice of India", "Prime minister", "Deputy speaker of Lok Sabha"],
    correct: "Deputy speaker of Lok Sabha",
    questionId: "97",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who among the following does not give his resignation to the president of India?   ",
    answers: ["Attorney General of India", "Governors of the states", "Comptroller and Auditor General of India", "Lok Sabha Speaker"],
    correct: "Lok Sabha Speaker",
    questionId: "98",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Lok Sabha speaker takes the oath of the office from ?   ",
    answers: ["Prime Minister", "President", "Chief Judge of Supreme Court", "No oath"],
    correct: "No oath",
    questionId: "99",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is not the pillar of Directive Principal of State Policy?   ",
    answers: ["Democratic principles", "Liberal principles", "Gandhian principles", "Socio-Economic principles"],
    correct: "Democratic principles",
    questionId: "100",
  },
]

var QuestionBank = (n = 1) =>
  Promise.resolve(QuestionList.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n))

export default QuestionBank